Hello.
Welcome back.
In this lesson, we shall see how to install some third packages into our estimate, 32 Chebet mix.
I'm going to open the Cuban mics we installed earlier.
Simply come over here a steam 32 and it's a piesse.
You click here.
And it says, cha cha cha cha re 32 bits detected Java G 64 bit as strongly advised with order to some
features might not be available.
So please install 64 bit.
So, Eddie, Jay, everyone's thought was a 32 bit.
The one that the link led us to.
So we've got to install 64 bit.
If you experience this sort of issue, then it's simple.
You simply need to install 64.
It is good that we are doing all of these things together so that you don't end up having roadblocks.
So you just come to Google, search Java or download GRV 64 bit in Google and or just.
Right.
Click on the first link to see what shows up.
Let's see.
Okay, it brings me here.
If it brings you to the documentation tab, just click on the download stuff.
Then let's see.
Download to pro me here.
Okay, so this that download tab, when you come here, the first time, it would look like this to
you, just scroll down to the bit where you see GRV over here.
Click Jeary Download.
And it brings us over here.
Oh.
Click here to accept the license agreement.
You can read up on this over here.
So click here.
Once it's accepted, come over here to download the O, download the dot e e version, Windows X 64
over here.
That's actually so click.
This one here.
It requires signing
a see.
We may have to create an account for or a coup or a coup.
Interesting.
OK.
So you've got to create an account and then proceed to download Chiari.
So I just locked in and to Jerry.
I started downloading as soon as I locked it.
So it turns out now even Oracle requires you to sign up before you can download things like the runtime
environments.
Bit ridiculous.
That's anyway.
Here we go.
Okay.
The installation is the download is complete, a double click here to install it.
Click Yes, over here.
This is from the Cuba mixed message, which is, of course, Cuba mix when it opens.
Course, we are installing that geography now.
It's hidden behind here.
We're just close.
Cuba makes it from here.
This terms.
Okay, quick next.
It's going to go through the same process again.
Right.
So now the download is complete list, check out Cubitt mix again.
Now that the download is complete.
Come over here.
And then I'm going to start SDM 32.
Cuba makes.
Okay, now we've been over.
No, we've been able to open successfully without that warning.
I'm gonna come over here to help.
Help.
Top over here and I'll click manage and better software packages.
And over here, we given a list of packages.
We've got iStore packages for the day microcontrollers that we're going to be generating code for.
So if you are going to be using your cube that makes for F zero, f1, f2, F3, F4, F.
You've got to install packages for each and every one of them.
You're going to be using EF four in this course.
So I'll come down here and I'm going to download the package for the esteemed 32 EF four series.
Well, right here, they've got different versions of the package.
I'm going to select the latest version over here by clicking here and I'll click install now.
And this is going to take a while squaddies to download this and then extract it.
So we've got a wait.
So to install other packages, I can come to the, um, tub to install The Simpsons package over here
on the SDM 32 MCU packages.
I installed the one for F for O come to arm and then I'm going to select the latest Simms's package
available and I'll click install now and it's going to go through the same process.
Right.
The installation of the packages is complete now, so click over here to close this or there was for
this lesson and I shall see you in the next lesson.